

JONAS COLAS

FULLSTACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+(54) 9 341 620 8912 +(54) 911 2704 0843



jonas.colas@yahoo.com https://github.com/jonas-colas https://linkedin.com/in/jonas-colas

PROFILE

I have more than 6 years of experience in the field of WebDevelopement, and Software Developement. Specialized in Backend Developement, Cloud Server AWS. Professional in Web Designing, Visualization, GUI, Graphics, etc. My Objective as a Software Developer are to continually increase my programming skills and my knowledge in computer science in order to present better solutions to my employers and their clients.

EDUCATION

- UNIVERSIDAD NACIONAL ROSARIO (2011-2014)
- Lic. Computer Sciences (C, C++, FORTRAN)
- POLOTECNOLOGICO ROSARIO (2012-2013)
- (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, PHP)
- EDUCACION IT ROSARIO (2016-2018)

(JavaScript, Jquery)

• UDEMY (2016-2018)

(Reactjs, Nodejs, Laravel, Python, Django)

SKILLS & QUALITIES

• FRONT-END

HTML
Bootstrap
JavaScript / Jquery
Vuejs / Nuxtjs
Reactjs / Nextjs

PHP / Laravel / Yii2

Node js / Express C / C++ Fortran

BACKEND

Python / Django

DATABASE

MySQL Post GreSQL Mongo DB • OTHERS

AWS Git Bitlab Gitlab

METHODOLOGY

SCRUM / Agile

LANGUAGES

Francais Español English



EXPERIENCES

HASHETAG DIGITAL AGENCY

Fron-End (February 2013 - October 2017)

• FREELANCING

Fullstack Developer (October 2017 - July 2018)

AENIMA SRL

Bckend Developer (August 2018 - March 2019)

• PILOT SOLUTION CRM

Backend Developer (March 2019 - August 2019)

• PREMINENS

Fullstack Developer (August 2019 - November 2019)

CODERS TEAM

Fullstack Developer (November 2019 - March 2020)